export const questionL3 = [
    {
      question: '9 * 1',
      choices: ['2', '8', '1', '9'],
      correctAnswer: '9',
    },
    {
      question: '2 * 6',
      choices: ['12', '13', '6', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: '12',
    },
    {
      question: '3 * 4',
      choices: ['8', '18', '4', '12'],
      correctAnswer: '12',
    },
    {
      question: '4 * 6',
      choices: ['21', '27', '12', '24'],
      correctAnswer: '24',
    },
    {
      question: '5 * 6',
      choices: ['26', '20', '15', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'None of the above',
    },
    {
      question: '6 * 9',
      choices: ['36', '24', '18', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'None of the above',
    },
    {
      question: '7 * 4',
      choices: ['27', '14', '18', '28'],
      correctAnswer: '28',
    },
    {
      question: '8 * 3',
      choices: ['24', '41', '14', '16'],
      correctAnswer: '24',
    },
    {
      question: '9 * 5',
      choices: ['25', '35', '40', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'None of the above',
    },
    {
      question: '3 * 9',
      choices: ['29', '37', '19', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'None of the above',
    },
    {
        question: '6 * 5',
        choices: ['30', '24', '42', '36'],
        correctAnswer: '30',
      },
      {
        question: '8 * 7',
        choices: ['28', '37', '63', '56'],
        correctAnswer: '56',
      },
      {
        question: '5 * 2',
        choices: ['15', '20', '40', '10'],
        correctAnswer: '10',
      },
      {
        question: '6 * 9',
        choices: ['48', '18', '30', '54'],
        correctAnswer: '54',
      },
      {
        question: '4 * 5',
        choices: ['22', '2', '18', 'None of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'None of the above',
      },
      {
        question: '9 * 4',
        choices: ['27', '36', '19', '42'],
        correctAnswer: '36',
      },
      {
        question: '3 * 6',
        choices: ['12', '28', '18', '24'],
        correctAnswer: '18',
      },
      {
        question: '3 * 9',
        choices: ['27', '24', '18', '9'],
        correctAnswer: '27',
      },
      {
        question: '5 * 7',
        choices: ['20', '45', '30', '35'],
        correctAnswer: '35',
      },
      {
        question: '7 * 7',
        choices: ['49', '21', '36', '63'],
        correctAnswer: '49',
      },
      {
        question: '8 * 9',
        choices: ['48', '72', '63', 'None of the above'],
        correctAnswer: '72',
      },
      {
        question: '8 * 8',
        choices: ['29', '37', '56', '64'],
        correctAnswer: '64',
      },
      {
        question: '4 * 4',
        choices: ['12', '28', '14', '16'],
        correctAnswer: '16',
      },
      {
        question: '5 * 5',
        choices: ['20', '21', '15', 'None of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'None of the above',
      },
      {
        question: '9 * 2',
        choices: ['29', '23', '19', 'None of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'None of the above',
      },
      {
          question: '7 * 4',
          choices: ['12', '21', '1', '28'],
          correctAnswer: '28',
        },
        {
          question: '7 * 6',
          choices: ['42', '33', '28', '35'],
          correctAnswer: '42',
        },
        {
          question: '5 * 10',
          choices: ['25', '30', '50', '35'],
          correctAnswer: '50',
        },
        {
          question: '6 * 6',
          choices: ['2', '13', '3', '36'],
          correctAnswer: '36',
        },
        {
          question: '8 * 4',
          choices: ['22', '42', '18', 'None of the above'],
          correctAnswer: 'None of the above',
        },
  ]
  export default questionL3